{
    "subject": "resource/The_Fall_of_the_Roman_Empire_(film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/cinematography",
    "object": "resource/Robert_Krasker",
    "human_readable": "The cinematography of 'The Fall of the Roman Empire' was done by Robert Krasker.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9473620057106018,
            "question": "Was Robert Krasker involved in the production of 'The Fall of the Roman Empire'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9257554411888123,
            "question": "Who was responsible for the cinematography of 'The Fall of the Roman Empire'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.901934802532196,
            "question": "What role did Robert Krasker play in 'The Fall of the Roman Empire'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8679067492485046,
            "question": "What film did Robert Krasker work on as a cinematographer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7988430857658386,
            "question": "Besides 'The Fall of the Roman Empire', what other films has Robert Krasker worked on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7447493672370911,
            "question": "Name a film that features the work of Robert Krasker."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38824760913848877,
            "question": "What is Robert Krasker's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20879055559635162,
            "question": "Can you name another film that features cinematography by a well-known professional?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19561699032783508,
            "question": "How does the cinematography of a film contribute to its overall impact?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14505447447299957,
            "question": "What are some important aspects of good cinematography in filmmaking?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The cinematography of 'The Fall of the Roman Empire' was done by Robert Krasker.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2942_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the cinematography of a film contribute to its overall impact?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2942_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name another film that features cinematography by a well-known professional?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2942_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Robert Krasker's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2942_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2942_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2942_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2942_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2942_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2942_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2942_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2942_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2942_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2942_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2942_5.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the documents mention that \"Krasker won his second award from the British Society of Cinematographers for his work on this film\", and also state that \"Cinematographer, Robert Krasker chose to utilize very little of the Roman forum in the finished film.\" The text explicitly mentions Robert Krasker's involvement as a cinematographer for 'The Fall of the Roman Empire'."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis answer is derived from the information provided, specifically in the document with file path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2942/re-ranker-msmarco/43.txt`, where it states: \"It was made in 1964 by the same team who made the classic adventure films El Cid and 55 Days at Peking. Samuel Bronston producer, Philip Yordan writer, and Anthony Mann director. (TFOTRE has one of the best casts ever assembled for a feature film.)\" And later, \"cinematographer, Robert Krasker chose to utilize very little of the Roman forum in the finished film. Even more of an oddity, his lack of artistic license did not particularly concern Bronston, who derived a certain amount of pleasure from entertaining visiting dignitaries.\" This information supports that Robert Krasker was indeed the cinematographer for \"The Fall of the Roman Empire\"."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}